http://www.kingscourtgalleries.co.uk/page/privacy

This site sets essential cookiesThis is okMore information
GO Basket Items: 0 | £0.00HomeAbout UsProductsFramingContactHomePrivacy PrivacyThis Privacy Policy sets out how we, Kings Court Galleries Limited, collect, store and use information about you when you use or interact with our website, https://www.kingscourtgalleries.co.uk (our website) and where we otherwise obtain or collect information about you.This Privacy Policy is effective from 27th April 2018ContentsSummaryOur detailsInformation we collect when you visit our websiteInformation we collect when you contact usInformation we collect when you place an order on our websiteOur use of automated decision-making and profilingHow we collect or obtain information about you from third partiesDisclosure and additional uses of your informationHow long we retain your informationHow we secure your informationTransfers of your information outside the European Economic AreaYour rights in relation to your informationYour right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes Sensitive Personal InformationChanges to our Privacy PolicyChildren's PrivacyCalifornia Do Not Track Disclosures CopyrightSummaryThis section summarises how we obtain, store and use information about you. It is intended to provide a very general overview only. It is not complete in and of itself and it must be read in conjunction with the corresponding full sections of this Privacy Policy.Data controller: Kings Court Galleries LimitedHow we collect or obtain information about you:
• when you provide it to us (e.g. by contacting us)• from your use of our website, using cookies, and• and occasionally from third partiesInformation we collect: first name, last name, email address, subject, comments, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, IP address, information about your computer or device (e.g. device and browser type), and information about how you use our website (e.g. which pages you have viewed, the time when you view them and what you clicked on).How we use your information: for administrative and business purposes (particularly to contact you) and in connection with our legal rights and obligations..Disclosure of your information to third parties: only to the extent necessary to run our business, to our service providers, to fulfil any contracts we enter into with you, where required by law or to enforce our legal rights.Do we sell your information to third parties (other than in the course of a business sale or purchase or similar event): NoHow long we retain your information: for no longer than necessary, taking into account any legal obligations we have (e.g. to maintain records for tax purposes), any other legal basis we have for using your information (e.g. your consent, performance of a contract with you or our legitimate interests as a business) and on the basis of certain additional criteria set out in the main section below entitled How long we retain your information. For specific retention periods in relation to certain information which we collect from you, please see the main section below entitled How long we retain your information.How we secure your information: using appropriate technical and organisational measures such as storing your information on secure servers, encrypting transfers of data to or from our servers using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, only granting access to your information where necessary.Use of cookies:This site only sets essential cookies.If there are any legacy non-essential cookies left on your browser from previous visits, please delete them by following the instructions in our cookies policy.For more information, please visit our cookies policyTransfers of your information outside the European Economic Area: we will only transfer your information outside the European Economic Area if we are required to do so by law. Where we do so, we will ensure appropriate safeguards are in place.Use automated decision making and profiling: we do not use automated decision making and/or profiling.Your rights in relation to your information
• to access your information and to receive information about its use
• to have your information corrected and/or completed
• to have your information deleted
• to restrict the use of your information
• to receive your information in a portable format
• to object to the use of your information
• to withdraw your consent to the use of your information• to complain to a supervisory authoritySensitive personal information: we do not knowingly or intentionally collect what is commonly referred to as 'sensitive personal information'. Please do not submit sensitive personal information about you to us. For more information, please see the main section below entitled Sensitive Personal Information.Return to topOur detailsThe data controller in respect of our website is Kings Court Galleries Limited.We are registered in England & Wales under registration number 05426254 and our registered office address is 14 Oakdale Road, Weybridge, Surrey KT13 8EJ.Our trading address is the same (or can be diffrerent)... it might also say the principal trading address.You can contact the data controller by writing to the trading address, completing the contact form or by sending an email to kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk.If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact the data controller.Return to topInformation we collect when you visit our websiteWe collect and use information from website visitors in accordance with this section and the section entitled Disclosure and additional uses of your information.Web server log informationWe use a third party server to host our website. Our website server automatically logs the IP address you use to access our website as well as other information about your visit such as the pages accessed information requested, the date and time of the request, the source of your access to our website (e.g. the website or URL (link) which referred you to our website), and your browser version and operating system.Our website server is based in the United Kingdom.Use of website server log information for IT security purposesOur third party hosting provider collects and stores server logs to ensure network and IT security and so that the server and website remain uncompromised. This includes analysing log files to help identify and prevent unauthorised access to our network, the distribution of malicious code, denial of services attacks and other cyber attacks, by detecting unusual or suspicious activity.Unless we are investigating suspicious or potential criminal activity, we do not attempt nor do we allow our website server provider to identify you or attempt to identify you from the information collected via server logs.Legal basis for processing: compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject (Article 6(1)(c) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legal obligation: recording access to our website using server log files is an appropriate technical measure to ensure a level of security appropriate to protect information collected by our website.Legal basis for processing: our and a third party's legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interest: we and our third party hosting provider have a legitimate interest in ensuring network and information security.Cookies and similar technologiesCookies are data files which are sent from a website to a browser to record information about users for various purposes.We use cookies on our website. For further information on how we use cookies, please see our cookies policy.
You can reject some or all of the cookies we use on or via our website by changing your browser settings. If we are intending to use non-essential cookies, they will be blocked by default, and you must provide explicit consent via our cookie control banner. Note that blocking essential cookies can impair your ability to use our website or some or all of its features. For further information about cookies, including how to change your browser settings, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org or see our cookies policy.Return to topInformation we collect when you contact usWe collect and use information from individuals who contact us in accordance with this section and the section entitled Disclosure of your information to third parties.EmailIf you contact us sending an email to the email address displayed on our website, we will collect your name and email address and any other information contained in the email you send us (for example, any information in your email signature (if applicable)).Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation). Legitimate interest(s): responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).
Transfer and storage of your informationMessages you send us are stored on our third party hosting provider's services in the United Kingdom.Contact formWhen you contact us using our contact form we collect the following mandatory information: first name, last name, email address, subject, messages.If you do not provide the mandatory information required by our contact form, you will not be able to submit it and we will not receive your enquiry.If you do not supply the optional information required by our contact form, we may not be able to respond to your enquiry effectively.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation) Legitimate interest(s): responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).Transfer and storage of your informationMessages you send us via our contact form are stored on our third party hosting provider's servers in the United Kingdom.PhoneWhen you contact us by phone, we collect your phone number and any information provide to us during your conversation with us.We do not record phone calls.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation) Legitimate interest(s): responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so.Transfer and storage of your informationInformation about your call, such as your phone number and the date and time of your call, is processed and stored by our third party telephone service provider which is located in the United Kingdom.PostIf you contact us by post, we will collect any information you provide to us in any postal communications you send us.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation) Legitimate interest(s): responding to enquiries and messages we receive and keeping records of correspondence.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where your message relates to us providing you with goods or services or taking steps at your request prior to providing you with our goods and services (for example, providing you with information about such goods and services), we will process your information in order to do so).Return to topInformation we collect when you place an order on our websiteWe collect and use information from individuals who place an order on our website in accordance with this section and the section entitled Disclosure and additional uses of your information.Information collected when you place an orderMandatory informationWhen you place an order for goods or services on our website, we collect the following information: email address, billing first name, billing last name, billing address, billing town, billing post code, shipping first name, shipping last name, shipping address, shipping town, shipping post code.If you do not provide this information, you will not be able to purchase goods or services from us on our website or enter into a contract with us.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation). Reason why necessary to perform a contract: we need the mandatory information collected by our checkout form to establish who the contract is with and to contact you to fulfil our obligations under the contract, including sending you receipts and order confirmations. Legal basis for processing: compliance with a legal obligation (Article 6(1)(c) of the General Data Protection Regulation). Legal obligation: we have a legal obligation to issue you with an invoice for the goods and services you purchased from us where you are VAT registered and we require the mandatory information collected by our checkout form for this purpose. We also have a legal obligation to keep accounting records, including records of transactions.Optional informationWe also collect optional information from you, such as: your telephone numberIf you do not supply the optional information requested at checkout, we will be unable to contact you to discuss your order.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation). Legitimate interests: to contact the customer by phone where (if necessary) in relation to their orderProcessing your paymentAfter you place an order on our website you will need to make payment for the goods or services you have ordered. In order to process your payment we use a third payment processor. Your payment will be processed by SagePay.SagePay collects, uses and processes your information, including payment information, in accordance with their privacy policy. You can access their privacy policy via the following link: https://www.sagepay.co.uk/policies/privacy-policyTransfer and storage of your informationSagePay is located in UK. Information relating to the processing of your payment is stored within the European Economic Area on SagePay servers in the UK.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: to fulfil your contractual obligation to pay for the goods or services you have ordered from us.Return to topOur use of automated decision-making and profilingWe do not use automated decision making or profiling.Return to topHow we collect or obtain information about you from third partiesThis section sets out how we obtain or collect information about you from third parties.Information received from third partiesGenerally, we do not receive information about you from third parties.It is possible, however that third parties with whom we have had no prior contact may provide us with information about you.Information we obtain from third parties will generally be your name and contact details, but will include any additional information about you which they provide to us.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where a third party has passed on information about you to us (such as your name and email address) in order for us to provide services to you, we will process your information in order to take steps at your request to enter into a contract with you and perform a contract with you (as the case may be).Legal basis for processing: consent (Article 6(1)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Consent: where you have asked that a third party to share information about you with us and the purpose of sharing that information is not related to the performance of a contract or services by us to you, we will process your information on the basis of your consent, which you give by asking the third party in question to pass on your information to us.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interests: where a third party has shared information about you with us and you have not consented to the sharing of that information, we will have a legitimate interest in processing that information in certain circumstances.For example, we would have a legitimate interest in processing your information to perform our obligations under a sub-contract with the third party, where the third party has the main contract with you. Our legitimate interest is the performance of our obligations under our sub-contract.Similarly, third parties may pass on information about you to us if you have infringed or potentially infringed any of our legal rights. In this case, we will have a legitimate interest in processing that information to investigate and pursue any such potential infringement.Where we receive information about you in errorIf we receive information about you from a third party in error and/or we do not have a legal basis for processing that information, we will delete your information.Information obtained by us from third partiesIn certain circumstances (for example, to verify the information we hold about you or obtain missing information we require to provide you with a service) we will obtain information about you from certain publicly accessible sources, both EU and non-EU, such as websites (including your own website if you have one) .Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract or to take steps at your request to enter into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: where you have entered into a contract or requested that we enter into a contract with you, in certain circumstances, we will obtain information about you from public sources in order to enable us to understand your business and provide services to you or services to a sufficient standard.For example, we would obtain and/or verify your email address from your website or from a directory where you ask us to send you information by email but we do not possess the information or we need to confirm that we have recorded your email address correctly.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interests: in certain circumstances, we will have a legitimate interest in obtaining information about you from public and private sources. For example, if you have infringed or we suspect that you have infringed any of our legal rights, we will have a legitimate interest in obtaining and processing information about you from such sources in order to investigate and pursue any suspected or potential infringement.Return to topDisclosure and additional uses of your informationThis section sets out the circumstances in which we will disclose information about you to third parties and any additional purposes for which we use your information.Disclosure of your information to service providersWe use a number of third parties to provide us with services which are necessary to run our business or to assist us with running our business, and who may process your information for us on our behalf. These include the following:• Telephone provider based in the UK• Web developer based in the UK• Hosting provider based in the UKYour information will be shared with these service providers where necessary to provide you with the service you have requested, whether that is accessing our website or ordering goods and services from us.We do not display the identities of our service providers publicly by name for security and competitive reasons. If you would like further information about the identities of our service providers, however, please contact us directly via kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk and we will provide you with such information where you have a legitimate reason for requesting it (where we have shared your information with such service providers, for example).Legal basis for processing: legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interest relied on: where we share your information with these third parties in a context other than where is necessary to perform a contract (or take steps at your request to do so), we will share your information with such third parties in order to allow us to run and manage our business efficiently.Legal basis for processing: necessary to perform a contract and/or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Reason why necessary to perform a contract: we may need to share information with our service providers to enable us to perform our obligations under that contract or to take the steps you have requested before we enter into a contract with you.Disclosure of your information to other third partiesWe disclose your information to other third parties in specific circumstances, as set out below.Sharing your information with third parties, which are either related to or associated with the running of our business, where it is necessary for us to do so. These third parties include our accountants. Further information on each of these third parties is set out below.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interest: running and managing our business efficiently.AccountantsWe share information with our accountants for tax purposes. For example, we share invoices we issue and receive with our accountants for the purpose of completing tax returns and our end of year accounts.Our accountants are located in the UK.We do not display the identities of the other third parties we may share information with by name for security and competitive reasons. If you would like further information about the identities of such third parties, however, please contact us directly via kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk and we will provide you with such information where you have a legitimate reason for requesting it (where we have shared your information with such third parties, for example).We will share your information with a prospective or actual purchaser or seller in the context of a business or asset sale or acquisition by us, a merger or similar business combination event, whether actual or potential.Legal basis for processing: legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation). Legitimate interest(s): sharing your information with a prospective purchaser, seller or similar person in order to allow such a transaction to take place.Disclosure of your information for legal reasonsIndicating possible criminal acts or threats to public security to a competent authorityIf we suspect that criminal or potential criminal conduct has been occurred, we will in certain circumstances need to contact an appropriate authority, such as the police. This could be the case, for instance, if we suspect that a fraud or a cyber crime has been committed or if we receive threats or malicious communications towards us or third parties.We will generally only need to process your information for this purpose if you were involved or affected by such an incident in some way.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interests: preventing crime or suspected criminal activity (such as fraud).In connection with the enforcement or potential enforcement our legal rightsWe will use your information in connection with the enforcement or potential enforcement of our legal rights, including sharing information with debt collection agencies if you do not pay amounts owed to us when you are contractually obliged to do so. Our legal rights may be contractual (where we have entered into a contract with you) or non-contractual (such as legal rights that we have under copyright law or tort law).Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interest: enforcing our legal rights and taking steps to enforce our legal rights.In connection with a legal or potential legal dispute or proceedingsWe may need to use your information if we are involved in a dispute with you or a third party for example, either to resolve the dispute or as part of any mediation, arbitration or court resolution or similar process.Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interest(s): resolving disputes and potential disputes.For ongoing compliance with laws, regulations and other legal requirementsWe will use and process your information in order to comply with legal obligations to which we are subject. For example, we may need to disclose your information pursuant to a court order or subpoena if we receive one.Legal basis for processing: compliance with a legal obligation (Article 6(1)(c) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legal obligation(s): legal obligations to disclose information which are part of the laws of [England and Wales] or if they have been integrated into the United Kingdom's legal framework (for example in the form of an international agreement which the United Kingdom has signed).Legal basis for processing: our legitimate interests (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation).Legitimate interest: where the legal obligations are part of the laws of another country and have not been integrated into the United Kingdom's legal framework, we have a legitimate interest in complying with these obligations.Return to topHow long we retain your informationThis section sets out how long we retain your information. We have set out specific retention periods where possible. Where that has not been possible, we have set out the criteria we use to determine the retention period.Retention periodsServer log information: we retain information on our server logs for 2 months.Correspondence and enquiries: when you make an enquiry or correspond with us for any reason, whether by email or via our contact form (if relevant) or by phone, we will retain your information for as long as it takes to respond to and resolve your enquiry, after which point we will delete your information.Criteria for determining retention periodsIn any other circumstances, we will retain your information for no longer than necessary, taking into account the following:• the purpose(s) and use of your information both now and in the future (such as whether it is necessary to continue to store that information in order to continue to perform our obligations under a contract with you or to contact you in the future);
• whether we have any legal obligation to continue to process your information (such as any record-keeping obligations imposed by relevant law or regulation);
• whether we have any legal basis to continue to process your information (such as your consent);
• how valuable your information is (both now and in the future);
• any relevant agreed industry practices on how long information should be retained;
• the levels of risk, cost and liability involved with us continuing to hold the information;
• how hard it is to ensure that the information can be kept up to date and accurate; and
• any relevant surrounding circumstances (such as the nature and status of our relationship with you).Return to topHow we secure your information We take appropriate technical and organisational measures to secure your information and to protect it against unauthorised or unlawful use and accidental loss or destruction, including:• only sharing and providing access to your information to the minimum extent necessary, subject to confidentiality restrictions where appropriate, and on an anonymised basis wherever possible;• using secure servers to store your information;• verifying the identity of any individual who requests access to information prior to granting them access to information;• using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software or other similar encryption technologies to encrypt any transfer of information between the website and the serverTransmission of information to us by emailTransmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure, and if you submit any information to us over the internet (whether by email, via our website or any other means), you do so entirely at your own risk.We cannot be responsible for any costs, expenses, loss of profits, harm to reputation, damages, liabilities or any other form of loss or damage suffered by you as a result of your decision to transmit information to us by such means. Return to topTransfers of your information outside the European Economic AreaAll of your information is stored in the following European Economic Area (EEA) countries: UK.Other than to comply with any legal obligations to which we are subject (compliance with a court order, for example), we do not intend to transfer your information outside the EEA or to an international organisation. In the unlikely event that we are required to transfer your information outside the EEA (or to an international organisation) for such a purpose, we will ensure appropriate safeguards and protections are in place.Return to topYour rights in relation to your informationSubject to certain limitations on certain rights, you have the following rights in relation to your information, which you can exercise by writing to us at or sending an email to
kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk• to request access to your information and information related to our use and processing of your information;
• to request the correction or deletion of your information;
• to request that we restrict our use of your information;
• to receive information which you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format (e.g. a CSV file) and the right to have that information transferred to another data controller (including a third party data controller);
• to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes (for further information, see the section below entitled Your right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposes); and
• to withdraw your consent to our use of your information at any time where we rely on your consent to use or process that information. Please note that if you withdraw your consent, this will not affect the lawfulness of our use and processing of your information on the basis of your consent before the point in time when you withdraw your consent.In accordance with Article 77 of the General Data Protection Regulation, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation.For the purposes of the UK, the supervisory authority is the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), the contact details of which are available here: https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/Further information on your rights in relation to your personal data as an individualThe above rights are provided in summary form only and certain limitations apply to many of these rights. For further information about your rights in relation to your information, including any limitations which apply, please visit the following pages on the ICO's website:• https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/ and
• https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/is-my-information-being-handled-correctly/You can also find out further information about your rights, as well as information on any limitations which apply to those rights, by reading the underlying legislation contained in Articles 12 to 22 and 34 of the General Data Protection Regulation, which is available here: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/reform/files/regulation_oj_en.pdfVerifying your identity where you request access to your informationWhere you request access to your information, we are required by law to use all reasonable measures to verify your identity before doing so.These measures are designed to protect your information and to reduce the risk of identity fraud, identity theft or general unauthorised access to your information.How we verify your identityWhere we possess appropriate information about you on file, we will attempt to verify your identity using that information.If it is not possible to identity you from such information, or if we have insufficient information about you, we may require original or certified copies of certain documentation in order to be able to verify your identity before we are able to provide you with access to your information.We will be able to confirm the precise information we require to verify your identity in your specific circumstances if and when you make such a request.Return to topYour right to object to the processing of your information for certain purposesYou have the following rights in relation to your information, which you may exercise in the same way as you may exercise by writing to the Data Controller or sending an email to
kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk:• to object to us using or processing your information where we use or process it in order to carry out a task in the public interest or for our legitimate interests, including 'profiling' (i.e. analysing or predicting your behaviour based on your information) based on any of these purposes; and
• to object to us using or processing your information for direct marketing purposes (including any profiling we engage in that is related to such direct marketing).You may also exercise your right to object to us using or processing your information for direct marketing purposes by:• clicking the unsubscribe link contained at the bottom of any marketing email we send to you and following the instructions which appear in your browser following your clicking on that link;• sending an email to kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk, asking that we stop sending you marketing communications or by including the words 'OPT OUT'.For more information on how to object to our use of information collected from cookies and similar technologies, please see the section entitled How to accept or reject cookies in our cookies policy, which is available here: /page/cookiesReturn to topSensitive Personal Information'Sensitive personal information' is information about an individual that reveals their racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic information, biometric information for the purpose of uniquely identifying an individual, information concerning health or information concerning a natural person's sex life or sexual orientation.We do not knowingly or intentionally collect sensitive personal information from individuals, and you must not submit sensitive personal information to us.If, however, you inadvertently or intentionally transmit sensitive personal information to us, you will be considered to have explicitly consented to us processing that sensitive personal information under Article 9(2)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation. We will use and process your sensitive personal information for the purposes of deleting it.Return to topChanges to our Privacy PolicyWe update and amend our Privacy Policy from time to time.Minor changes to our Privacy PolicyWhere we make minor changes to our Privacy Policy, we will update our Privacy Policy with a new effective date stated at the beginning of it. Our processing of your information will be governed by the practices set out in that new version of the Privacy Policy from its effective date onwards.Major changes to our Privacy Policy or the purposes for which we process your informationWhere we make major changes to our Privacy Policy or intend to use your information for a new purpose or a different purpose than the purposes for which we originally collected it, we will notify you by email (where possible) or by posting a notice on our website.We will provide you with the information about the change in question and the purpose and any other relevant information before we use your information for that new purpose.Wherever required, we will obtain your prior consent before using your information for a purpose that is different from the purposes for which we originally collected it.Return to topChildren's PrivacyBecause we care about the safety and privacy of children online, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying regulations protect the privacy of children using the internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect information from persons under the age of 18. The website is not intended to solicit information of any kind from persons under the age of 18.It is possible that we could receive information pertaining to persons under the age of 18 by the fraud or deception of a third party. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will, where required by law to do so, immediately obtain the appropriate parental consent to use that information or, if we are unable to obtain such parental consent, we will delete the information from our servers. If you would like to notify us of our receipt of information about persons under the age of 18, please do so by sending an email to kcgsales@kingscourtgalleries.co.uk.Return to topCalifornia Do Not Track Disclosures'Do Not Track' is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on a Do Not Track signal in their browser, the browser sends a message to websites requesting that they do not track the user. For information about Do Not Track, please visit www.allaboutdnt.orgAs we do not use any tracking cookies on this site, we do not respond to Do Not Track requests received from browsers at this time.Return to topCopyrightThis Privacy Policy is based on a General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/769) (GDPR) compliant template.The copyright in this Privacy Policy is either owned by, or licensed to, us and is protected by copyright laws around the world and copyright protection software. All intellectual property rights in this document are reserved.Return to topQuick LinksPrivacyCookiesTerms Of Website UseHelpDeliveryTerms And ConditionsSecuritySocial MediaPayment Methods ContactKings Court Galleries
949-953 Fulham Road
London SW6 5HYTel: 0207 610 6939© Kings Court Galleries 2020Web Design & Development By Web Preference
